✔ invalid covariance noise is rejected even when dropout skips correction (4.0176ms)
✔ invalid world and seed inputs are rejected; zero actual noise remains valid (2.0155ms)
✔ explicit variance mapping preserves exact squared matches, zero and independent movement (0.4956ms)
✔ scene bounds contain negative truth, fixes, dead reckoning, baseline and both uncertainty edges (1.062ms)
✔ match keeps exact variances, same data and baseline, including q=0; world changes clear baseline (10.9027ms)
✔ scrub is paused in seconds, leaves data unchanged, updates endpoint controls and removes stale summary (5.7698ms)
✔ same-data gain responds to R while noise matching help reflects tuning (5.9899ms)
Actual seed-42 scores: {"nominal":{"sensor":0.8293703884070283,"filter":0.1926924180432113,"dead":4.906345826662991,"coverage":99.66666666666667,"fixes":300,"steps":300},"dropout":{"sensor":0.8401810980307293,"filter":0.23634380647390774,"dead":4.906345826662991,"coverage":98.33333333333333,"fixes":220,"steps":300},"current":{"sensor":0.8293703884070283,"filter":0.35129557368207154,"dead":15.916042409512883,"coverage":76,"fixes":300,"steps":300},"bias":{"sensor":1.795451982752978,"filter":1.6179357706512916,"dead":4.906345826662991,"coverage":33.333333333333336,"fixes":300,"steps":300}}
✔ exact predict/correct fixture uses velocity cross covariance and Joseph correction (0.9796ms)
✔ Q is discrete held-acceleration covariance q B B transpose (0.0975ms)
✔ dropout is exactly prediction-only and grows depth uncertainty (2.3049ms)
✔ seed replay is deterministic; tuning never changes truth, commands or fixes (5.0723ms)
✔ truth is never consumed by the filter (1.2044ms)
✔ actual sensor noise changes fixes only; actual acceleration noise changes physics (1.147ms)
✔ scenario disturbances are explicit, bounded in time, and preserve random draws (1.2482ms)
✔ covariance stays finite, symmetric and positive semidefinite over 100000 steps (50.6473ms)
✔ seed 42 nominal has meaningful fixed RMSE; mismatch need not improve (2.082ms)
✔ RMSE handles no samples, missing fixes and differing denominators honestly (0.6584ms)
✔ arbitrary files preserve bytes, type, original name and private metadata (30.2309ms)
✔ downloads, previews, metadata and deletion require the uploading session (1.576ms)
✔ raster images preview inline and also download with the original name (1.056ms)
✔ HTML, SVG and executable content remain attachments even with preview requested (1.9232ms)
✔ 10 MB limit applies to every type, accepts the boundary and rejects excess (39.2389ms)
✔ invalid and missing multipart file input returns a useful error (0.803ms)
✔ existing image field, URLs and bucket records remain usable and deletable (2.9178ms)
✔ both upload page paths establish a private session cookie (1.9477ms)
✔ voltage readout links to the hidden page and keeps its default value (0.7344ms)
✔ four cards open existing projects in new tabs and the footer matches (1.3923ms)
✔ all local stylesheets and scripts resolve for the hidden page (0.2359ms)
✔ secret page uses natural document scrolling and a responsive card column (1.3223ms)
✔ clicking the readout navigates after the shared transition (1.0322ms)
✔ changed voltage keeps the link functional (0.4393ms)
✔ modified clicks keep native browser behavior (1.6662ms)
✔ reduced motion navigates immediately (0.9702ms)
✔ keyboard shortcuts leave the slider and readout keys alone (0.592ms)
✔ hidden page initializes without homepage controls and returns home (0.6138ms)
✔ back/forward restoration clears leaving and activation states (0.4518ms)
✔ existing Worker routing serves the hidden page, projects, and assets (24.1259ms)
ℹ tests 37
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 37
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 139.1051
